Iván Urra

Full Stack Web Developer

I am a Full Stack Web Developer. I like to solve problems and I am excited about the possibilities that technology offers to help people. I value commitment, hard work, and motivation to learn something new every day. I love teamwork and helping others. I have worked for more than ten years in highly regulated IT environments.

Technologies & Methodologies

JavaScript PostgreSQL React JS Docker Next JS Kubernetes

Node JS AWS

Express JS Git & GitHub

HTML Agile
(S)CSS SCRUM
MongoDB ITIL

Education

2020

Full Stack Web Development Graduate

Ironhack

Learned Frontend and Backend technologies.

2002 - 2006

Bachelor's degree, Tourism

University Carlos III of Madrid

2000 - 2002

FP Higher Degree: Application Development

I.E.S. Ciudad Escolar

Languages

Spanish: Native English: B2

Contact

https://ivanurra.dev

ivan.urra.dev@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/ivanurra github.com/ivanurra

Relevant Experience

AUG 2021 - PRESENT REMOTE

Full Stack Web Developer

@ Secuoyas

- → Write modern, performant, clean and maintainable code for a diverse array of client.
- → Work with a variety of different languages and frameworks such as JavaScript, React, Gatsby and Next.
- → Communicate and collaborate with multi-disciplinary teams of engineers, designers, and stakeholders on a daily basis.

MAR 2021 - AUG 2021 MADRID

Full Stack Web Developer

@ Auro Group

- ♣ Built and shipped the new Auro website.
- Worked closely with designer and commercial team to develop the website using JavaScript, Vue, Nuxt and Vuetify.
- Developed and maintained code for in-house projects primarily.

MAR 2019 - MAR 2021

PALMA, ILLES BALEARS

IT Support Technician

@ Iberostar Group

- ◆ Performed high-level support to more than 50 hotels in EMEA countries.
- ★ Facilitated Cloud software installation and configuration in updates or openings of new hotels.
- → Reduced helpdesk tickets by 60%.

JAN 2016 - FEB 2017

MADRID

IT Support Manager Europe & Asia

@ LATAM Airlines

- → Managed a cross-functional team of 5 in 3 locations (Madrid, Frankfurt and Paris).
- ★ Led operational continuity of all systems and services that support business processes in Europe.
- Reduced customer support calls by 80% and increased satisfaction by 90%.